misspatina.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy & Cookies – Miss Patina

We greatly respect your privacy and personal information, so we only save the information we need and will ensure that it is saved as securely as possible, is up-to-date, and is relevant to you. Here’s why we need it and how we use it.

### How we use your name and contact details

| 

### Why?  
  
---|---  
To deliver your purchases to you | When you make a purchase, we require your name and contact details so we can make the delivery, we save this information so that we know who has made a purchase from us  
For your customer account | When you create a customer account with us, we save your name and contact details so that we know who has made a purchase from us.  
To contact you about our current promotions and offers via email | When you sign up to our newsletter, we save your name and contact details so that we can send our unique offers and promotions to you  
For our Mail Chimp form | Our emails are made using Mail Chimp marketing service and they store your email addresses on our behalf when you sign up to the newsletter  
  
### How we use your card details and billing information

| 

### Why?  
  
---|---  
To take payments and give refunds | When you make a purchase or are refunded, we will use your card information  
  
### How we use your order history and saved items

| 

### Why?  
  
---|---  
To make it easier to buy from Miss Patina | When you add an item to the cart, you can go back to it later to make your purchase using your saved items  
To check whether your order has been delivered and to process returns | This information is needed to properly manage your orders and returns  
  
### Your rights relating to your personal information  
  
---  
  
  * The right to be informed about how your personal information is being used

  * The right to access the personal information we hold about you

  * The right to request the correction of inaccurate personal information we hold about you

  * The right to request that we delete your data, or stop processing it or collecting it, in some circumstances

  * The right to stop direct marketing messages, and to withdraw consent for other consent-based processing at any time

  * The right to request that we transfer or port elements of your data either to you or another service provider

  * The right to complain to your data protection regulator, in the UK it is the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO)

### Marketing messages  
  
---  
If you no longer want to receive our marketing emails then you can unsubscribe from our mailing list by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email  
  
### Cookie policy  
  
---  
We may store information about you using cookies (files which are sent by us to your computer or other access device) which we can access when you visit our site in future. We do this in order to learn more about our valued customers.If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies.Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site.
